# Nazanin Akbari . Jarvis Consulting

My bachelor degree is in the field of Biomedical engineering. I have two years of work experience as a biomedical engineer in 5Azar hospital, Gorgan, Iran. I started my master degree at Concordia university, Montreal, QC in 2019. I got my master degree from Concordia university in the field of Electrical Engineering and Computer Science. At Concordia university, I did multiple projects in signal processing, image processing, Hardware verification and designing website for Airline reservation system. In Montreal, I also learned French language, B1 level. I like software industry because this field is incredibly broad. I am passionate to learn new things and expand my knowledge and experience. I love to solve problems and help people to experience a better and easier life.

### Skills

Proficient: Java, Python, Google Cloud Platform, Linux/Bash, Visual Studio

Competent: Agile/Scrum, RDBMS/SQL, Git, Docker and Containerization, Intellij IDE

Familiar: Neural Network, Machine Learning, C#, Azure DevOps, Unit testing

## **Jarvis Projects**

Project source code: https://github.com/jarviscanada/jarvis\_data\_eng\_NazaninAkbari

Linux Cluster Resource Monitoring App [GitHub]: Implemented Linux-SQL project, to help Jarvis Linux Cluster Administration (LCA) record the hardware specification of 10 servers running CentOS7 which are connected to each other throughout a switch. The project is implemented by using Bash scripts, Docker containers, Postgres database, and SQL queries.

### **Highlighted Projects**

Website for Airline reservation system: Designed an Airline Reservation System application which enables the customers to search and book the flights in general. The project has been designed in C# technology and consists of a SQL server as the database of the project.

#### Professional Experiences

Software Developer, Jarvis (2021-present): Developed a monitoring system with Postgres database.

Biomedical engineer, 5Azar hospital, Gorgan, Iran (2016-2018): As a biomedical engineer: I was responsible for eight direct employees, I analyze technical defects and implement data-driven solution with engineering guidance, Prioritizes work load effectively and complete all work assignments in a timely manner, Control my team member hours to hit monthly targets while maintaining above 100% productivity, I always took responsibility of situations and errors of myself or my team members, Insisted on highest standards (I never cut the corners), Eager to learn more and improvement

#### Education

Concordia university (2019-2021), Master of Electrical engineering and Computer Science, Electrical and Computer Engineering - GPA: 3.6/4.3

Azad university, Tehran, Iran (2013-2016), Bachelor of Biomedical Engineering, Electrical and Computer Engineering - Identified as exceptional talent, Azad University, Tehran, Iran (2014) - GPA: 3.62/4.3 - Scholarship

### Miscellaneous

- Udemy Scrum certificate (2021)
- Reading
- Walking
- Cooking